♪ Mm mm mm mm ♪ The boss man's yellin'.
My desk's a mess.
Deadlines circlin'.
I confess.
The coffee's cold.
My patience thin.
This nine to five feels like a sin.
But then I see her.
That red headed light.
Her smile burns through my darkest night.
Oh oh oh oh hallelujah.
I'm gonna be all right.
Ooh hallelujah.
Two boys screamin'.
The house is wild.
Spilled milk,
rivers and tantrum trials.
I'm just one man.
I feel so small.
How do I answer their every call?
But then I see her.
That red headed light.
Her smile burns through my darkest night.
Oh oh oh oh hallelujah.
I'm gonna be all right.
Woo!
Hallelujah.
I'm gonna be all right.
Breath is short.
My chest is tight.
The walls are closin'.
I lose the fight.
The world spins fast.
I'm on my knees.
I cry for help.
Lord,
hear me,
please.
But then I see her.
That red headed light.
Oh oh,
her smile burns through my darkest night.
Oh oh oh oh hallelujah.
I'm gonna be all right.
Oh hallelujah.